

# **EDUARDO PINEDA**

edibozu@gmail.com | 706-618-2155 | Augusta, GA 30906

### Summary

Current student enrolled in Georgia Tech's Coding Bootcamp. Hoping for an opportunity in said field, as soon as graduation. Previous job experience shows versatility and adaptability to changing environments. Looking forward to a bright future and my next challenge.

#### Skills

Erection drawing assessments
Safety measures
Job site preparation
Heavy lifting
First Aid/CPR
Team management
Process improvement

Inventory management

Team building
Organization
Problem Solving
Working well with others
HTML
CSS
JavaScript

### Experience

Iron Workers Local 846 | Aiken, SC **Union Ironworker** 07/2016 - 04/2020

- Working with both my hands and mind, to get tasks done, in a timely and uniform matter.
- Worked at heights, off of scaffolds, while wearing a harness.
- Had to lift 50+ lbs. on several occasions to move material to work area and also to install the rebar.
- Worked, in unison, with crew members to accomplish the tasks placed in front of us. Developed extraordinary communication skills while having other crafts working around us and heavy noise.
- Took blueprints and diagrams and constructed the the desired design, built th specs, while also working around other craft's previous work.

Advance Auto Parts | Dalton, GA Assistant General Manager 12/2010 - 06/2016

- Keyholder, which meant i opened and closed the store and had access to safe and security codes.
- In charge on inventory, ordering products that were needed at the store and also organizing stock.
- On occasion, would make the week's work schedule, based on customer traffic patterns and hours available to me, assuring that we always had plenty of coverage.
- Had to develop a friendly work relationship with our regular DIY customers as well as with our commercial, professional accounts, to ensure their future business.
- Organized and handed out tasks to crew members, and oversaw operation, to keep business running smoothly.

Whitfield County Fire Dept. | Dalton, GA
Volunteer Firefighter

- Received specialized training in CPR, Oxygen Administration, Haz Mat Awareness, Haz Mat Ops, and received Firefighter 1 certification.
- Carried around a pager, where the same calls as the station, came through.. When available, I would assist the full-time firefighters and EMT first responders, when it was a medical call.
- Developed a bond with my fellow classmates during the trainee course. We would train in a burning, controlled unit to simulate a real life situation.

## **Education and Training**

08/2008 - 03/2010

Dalton State College | Dalton, GA **Some College (No Degree)** in Physics/Pre-Engineering

Georgia Tech Coding Boot Camp | Atlanta, GA Coding

Expected in 11/2020

#### Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardo-pineda-5595431b6/

• GitHub: https://github.com/Edibozu